Professor Fang.
Don't jump!
Boss, bosses...
Let me, let me, let me say a few words.
Okay, okay, okay.
Who the hell are you, kid?
Bie Fan.
"Don't be annoying"? How can I not be annoyed?!
Do you know how much I...
how much I prepared for today?
I was so close to making it.
And you ruined it all!
Why are you being so loud?
My name is Bie Fan.
I'm a fan of his.
The three elements of success are:
persistence...
Alright, stop reciting.
My mom and I met you together.
Do you remember?
Professor Fang.
Do you remember my mom?
Buddy,
are... are you...
you know, a little...
like, different from...
other people?
Like, really...
Do you know what I mean?
This child,
compared to other kids,
is very, very...
Doctor!
Why... why is...
why is this child's head at the bottom?
You're holding him upside down.
What's his name?
Bie Fan. Didn't you name him?
Right, right, right. This is my son.
My mom said,
other babies cry when they're born,
but you're laughing.
I cried a lot.
You don't need to start from that far back.
Actually, I... I mostly want to know...
when... when did you start...
perusing my work?
Do you know the word "peruse"? See? See? See?
Peruse...
See what? That year, I was born.
Born?
My book wasn't even out when you were born!
I'm having an academic discussion here.
Don't keep interrupting me.
What is Success?, page 19:
"Success must have a beginning and an end."
Regarding when I
started perusing Professor Fang's work,
I must start from the beginning.
When I was three years old,
I was the fastest kid in class at solving Tangrams.
This kid, Bie Fan,
is just too special.
A genius!
Later, I went to elementary school.
This kid is good at solving the Tangram,
but he can't just solve it
from first grade all the way to sixth grade.
He's played with that Tangram so much it's got a patina.
If your child still
only knows how to solve the Tangram,
then that's really weird.
Later, my dad took me to get my IQ tested.
Einstein's IQ
is here.
An average kid's IQ is here.
Your child's IQ
is here.
In other words,
your child
is half an Einstein.
Why don't you
get tested too?
So what if they're both 78?
Aren't I living just fine?
Your dad.
His name just wasn't good.
He was named Bie Yongsheng.
Then, later on...
Because I lost a fight with a classmate at school.
Stop right there!
My mom came to our school.
to sell box lunches.
From now on, I'll be selling box lunches here.
If anyone bullies my son again,
I'll chop their hands off!
You hear me?
Yes, ma'am.
And then, even later on...
My good friend, Rong Sihai,
gave me a secret martial arts manual.
While I was practicing moves in class,
the professor caught me.
Bie Fan!
We're about to prep for the college entrance exam!
What are you doing all day...
Come here, squat down for me.
While being scolded by the professor in the office,
I saw Professor Fang's book.
Just read this.
It's still better than reading about this condor!
Your... your professor...
really thinks like this?
Don't interrupt.
Can you let me finish?
Let the kid finish speaking.
You've had it hard since you were little.
Always getting bullied.
And didn't have many friends.
Ever since you read Professor Book's Fang...
F- Professor Fang's book,
your life started to change, right?
I wasn't interrupting.
Let me finish what I was saying.
I've been bullied since I was little,
and had hardly any friends.
It was after reading Professor Book's Fang...
Fang... Old Fang...
after Professor Book's Fang...
that my life began to change.
Mom, the professor said
the two of us aren't cut out for regular high school.
Then what are you cut out for?
Cut out for entering the workforce early.
Food, boss!
Coming!
Food's ready, food's ready!
Bie Fan, look at how busy your mom is every day.
Thanks! You don't even offer to help her.
How can I help her?
You could learn to be a chef,
and help her cook and stuff.
So I'll learn to be a chef,
and help her cook.
Then what do you want to do in the future?
I'm going to test into Tsinghua!
What's Tsinghua?
Page 69 of What is Success?,
Perseverance.
Perseverance is also an essential virtue for success.
Genius.
Done. Good.
A genius!
The author of What is Success?
actually replied to me!
Sihai.
Look.
Writer Haowen says,
"Keep it up!"
You finally finished reading it.
I memorized the whole thing.
Last page, third sentence.
"Life isn't always what it seems.
You must brave the wind and rain step by step,
taste all the bitterness of the world,
to realize impermanence is the only constant."
Page five, ninth sentence.
"Success is having the power of speech,
while being willing to let others hear your voice."
Page 50, sentence 24.
"Success is breathing fresh air.
Whether you're in a city office building
or on a stock exchange floor,
the air you breathe deeply
will always be refreshing."
This carving is really great!
I announce,
the winner of this King of Chefs Championship is Bie Fan!
And then you succeeded.
No, my success isn't because of the award,
but because of
your validation, Professor Fang.
Didn't bring it.
I think I did.
Do you... Do you want me to help you find it?
Professor Fang, don't touch my things.
Okay?
Is... Is this...
Isn't this that Nine-Turn...
I'm not tasting it.
You even ate one back then.
I succeeded.
Mom.
The darkest period of my life,
I relied on Professor Fang's book
to keep me going.
Mom?
Are you done pooping?
Are you done pooping or what?
What's wrong?
Mom! Sis, are you okay?
Hello, is this 120?
Son,
go buy me a sugary drink.
Mom might have low blood sugar.
Hurry up.
Go buy it.
Lung cancer. Terminal stage.
No way.
I don't even smoke.
Is it curable?
Hard to say.
It depends on how the surgery goes.
How much will it cost?
About 200,000.
What?
Did you look at the balance on my bank card
when you said that?
Mom, Uncle Zhang down the street said
these all cure low blood sugar.
Cure low blood sugar?
That little shop of your Uncle Zhang's
will go out of business sooner or later.
Son,
Mom needs to be hospitalized for checkups.
Take good care of yourself at home.
I made you dumplings and froze them in the fridge.
Boil some yourself when you're hungry.
And your change of clothes,
I've laid them all out on the bed for you.
Take off your dirty clothes
and leave them there.
Mom will wash them for you when I get back, okay?
Stop fussing with that.
There are doctors and nurses here.
Hurry, go to school.
I... I don't want to go to school.
You don't want to go? What do you want to do?
When I went to school before,
Mom sold box lunches at the gate to stay with me.
Now I want to stay downstairs
and sell box lunches to stay with Mom.
You have to go to school.
Selling box lunches is a dead end.
Do you hear me?
You need to study hard.
"What is Success?", page 34:
Success is not defined by others,
but living out your own meaning.
What disease did Auntie say she has?
My mom said she has low blood sugar.
And then?
Did your mom get better?
Later, my mom passed away.
I'm not cooking! I'm not cooking!
Let me pour you a drink.
No, no, let me. I'm the junior here.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Gao Guilan.
The one cooking right now...
must be my son, Bie Fan.
I told you I shouldn't cook!
Today,
I don't know how many friends and family came to see me off,
but I know
my son might not be the best host.
I hope you can all forgive him.
He is a very special child,
but he's warm, devoted,
kind, and honest.
I also hope every guest here
won't be too sad.
Birth, aging, illness, and death are inevitable.
Lastly, I hope you all eat and drink well.
And I also beg you all,
in the days to come,
to be kind to my son.
Thank you all.
Bie Fan,
Mom has never left you.
Mom just found a different way
to stay by your side forever.
Do you still remember
what Mom said to you before leaving?
Read it out loud to our friends and family.
My condolences.
Family returns the bow.
Family...
Mom, I miss you.
Aunt Zhang, Uncle Wang.
Is the food to your taste?
It's great. Really good.
Dad, about what I mentioned last time...
Do you remember?
I want to open a restaurant with Bie Fan.
Aunt Zhang and Uncle Wang even said they'd sponsor me.
Shouldn't you chip in a little too?
You're opening a restaurant with an idiot?
Do you really think that's gonna work?
Are you just trying to take our money...
...and throw it down the drain?
He's not an idiot.
I won't let you call him an idiot.
Fine, fine! He's not an idiot.
You're the idiot!
I'm not an idiot either!
But I won't let you call him an idiot!
Who do you think you're talking to?
Stop it, just stop.
I'll say whatever I want, you hear me?
You know damn well if he's an idiot or not!
Bie Fan.
Please don't mind him.
Lao Rong, calm down.
Let's talk about this another day.
You two can discuss this at home.
First Prize, National Sichuan Cuisine Competition.
First Prize, National Cantonese Cuisine Competition.
First Prize, National Hunan Cuisine Competition.
First Prize, National Pastry Competition.
Champion, National Chef Competition.
If we're comparing brains,
then Uncle Einstein is up here,
and I'm down here.
But if we're comparing cooking,
then I'm up here,
and Uncle Einstein is down here.
I wanna open a restaurant too.
Page 34 of "What is Success?":
"Success is not defined by others,
but by living out your own meaning."
The food is burnt.
Three!
Two!
Grand opening special! One!
Come on in!
Hey, Sanjiang!
You opened this restaurant?
My son and his buddy Da Congming
opened it together.
I have a small stake in it too.
It's super good. Try it.
Great! Wishing you prosperity!
Aunt Zhang is here! Come on in!
Hurry inside and order whatever you like!
Come on, right this way.
Alright, coming, coming.
Coming.
Here, try this.
Here it comes.
Try it, have a taste.
My restaurant is the best
restaurant back home.
Business is great every day.
Your rating is pretty high.
Moonlight
is proof of the sun and moon's love.
The horizon
One, two, lift!
is where the sky
and the earth hold hands.
Your original intention
is the destination of my dreams.
Only by tracing stroke by stroke,
across endless mountains and rivers,
until
you no longer care if you arrive.
How did you arrive here?
I'm a new streamer.
Today I ran into washed-up author Fang Haowen jumping off a roof.
It's my honor.
Babes in the chat,
remember to hit follow.
If any big bosses
want to gift me a Family Carnival,
let me see it.
That would be even better.
Thank you, thank you.
Fang Haowen's work,
publisher of What is Success?
Thank you, thank you.
I don't want you to die.
Why don't you want him to die?
I'll summarize it for you.
It's because his book changed you,
helped you,
and you think it can help more people.
I think his book changed me,
helped me,
and can help more people.
Thanks to "Fellow Sufferer"
for sending the big rocket.
If everyone wants to keep following
Fang Haowen's true fan,
Bie... Bie... Bie...
Bie Fan.
Bie Fan's true story,
please keep watching our stream.
Views! The views are going up!
The views!
You are very successful.
No, YOU are very successful.
Yes, you are very successful.
I am very successful.
Louder. I am very successful!
I am very successful!
Louder!
I am very successful! I am very successful!
I am very successful!
Successful! Successful! Successful!
Alright, today's stream is ending.
Please pre-register in the top left
for Bie Fan and Fang Haowen's stream.
Goodbye, family.
Successful!
Alright, alright, alright.
Good.
Come on, everyone, listen to me.
Today's stream hit a new record!
Our planner
said our stream today
reached how many viewers?
300,000 concurrent viewers.
Over 10 million total views.
Wait, wait. Let me ask real quick.
Where did you find this kid?
Come here.
Bro, come here. Come here.
Wait, what's wrong?
You come with me. Come with me.
What's wrong, Mr. Lei?
Well, he's... he's my artist.
My signed artist.
Bie... Bie Fan.
He studied... studied acting professionally.
You signed... signed... signed him?
I signed him. I signed him a long time ago.
This... I... all of this I was...
I was just...
Why didn't you tell me?
No, I... I...
This is great!
I really... Oh my god!
So... I didn't expect this shoot to go so well!
Buddy, we gotta hug.
Mr. Lei, let's collaborate more from now on.
We've got plenty of artists.
Alright.
Congratulations to us both.
Congratulations for what?
Finding the Key to popularity.
Mr. Lei, are you acting or really crying?
He's an idol.
Before I go,
let me say a few more things to you.
As you know,
Bie Fan is a bit special.
After I'm gone, he'll have no one to rely on.
And no one to take care of him.
You are good brothers to each other.
You must cherish that.
Help him open a restaurant.
I have 200,000 here.
I don't know if it's enough.
Don't worry, Auntie.
I'll figure something out for the rest of the money.
I promised you.
I swear.
My friendship with Bie Fan
will last forever.
Good.
Thank you.
Go call Bie Fan in.
I want to say a few words to him.
Bie Fan, your Mom is calling you.
Come here.
Come here, son.
Come sit over here. Come on.
I'm going to see your dad.
To the place with flowers,
grass, and rainbows.
Mom.
Are you going to leave me?
Mom won't leave you.
Mom will always, always be by your side.
Just in a different way.
Son.
There's nothing special about you.
You're just like everyone else.
The only thing special about you
is that you're too kind.
So from now on, you need to protect yourself.
Take good care of yourself.
Coming!
Add a Mapo Tofu.
Got it, Uncle. Coming!
Mapo Tofu.
Add a moderate amount of oil to the wok.
Peanut oil is best.
Peanut oil adds a nice fragrance.
Once the oil is hot,
add the minced meat.
Stir-fry the meat until it's golden.
Then add a spoonful of cooking wine.
Cooking wine removes the raw smell.
And then,
add two spoonfuls of Spicy broad bean paste.
Remember, it must be two spoonfuls.
Any more and it'll be too salty.
As for the eggplant,
you must use roll-cutting.
This way, the flesh inside
won't turn black.
One more thing,
you need to add plenty of oil.
Eggplants absorb a lot of oil.
Don't add water.
If you add water, it won't taste good.
Like this, use that oil to...
stir-fry, stir-fry, stir-fry it hard.
Stir-fry it until it's fragrant and flavorful.
Bie Fan, just focus on cooking.
Mom's waiting for you to come home from work.
Welcome to Fang Haowen's livestream debut,
a mega giveaway event!
Hello, everyone in the stream!
Here's Along bringing you
something you've never heard before:
the Velociraptor version of "The Moon Went Too Far"!
Take a good look at my book.
My book!
What's wrong with me?
You savages!